casualmale.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Statement | DXL

Last updated August 2018

## NOTICE TO INDIVIDUALS RESIDING IN THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA ("EEA") OR SWITZERLAND, PLEASE READ THIS IMPORTANT NOTICE BEFORE USING THIS SITE.

This site is intended for residents of the United States. If you reside in a country in the EEA or Switzerland, you may use this site, but you need to be aware that this site is not intended to be subject to or governed by the General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR"). Rest assured, however, that if you use this site to purchase product from us, your purchase transaction will be handled through our independent third-party service provider, Borderfree, which is GDPR compliant. Borderfree does not share your personal information with us. For more about Borderfree, [click here](https://www.borderfree.com/). If you are a resident of Switzerland or a country in the EEA and you read this policy, you will read about "cookies". Although cookies will be employed by us as you browse our site, we will not be using those cookies for any reason, because we are not marketing to any address which is in the EEA or Switzerland.

## FOR U.S. CUSTOMERS

Destination XL Group, Inc. ("DXL") recognizes your concerns regarding the collection and use of personal information, and we want our visitors to know that DXL has taken important steps to safeguard your privacy and security. This Privacy Statement describes the information that we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, the instances when we share it with third-parties and the measures we employ to protect such information.

While this Privacy Statement applies primarily to our online and wireless service practices, certain practices including, but not limited to, the collection, use, and sharing of information with others, may be applicable and extend to our offline practices. By shopping in our stores, through our promotional mailers, wireless service, or visiting DestinationXL.com, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Statement.

This privacy statement is from:

 **Destination XL Group, Inc.**  
555 Turnpike Street  
Canton, MA 02021  
United States of America

* * *

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### Automatic Information:

When you visit DestinationXL.com, our server attaches a small text file, known as a "cookie", to your computer's hard drive which will automatically collect and store information such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the browser software you use and your operating system, the date and time you access our website, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website, if any. This information collected by using a cookie is sometimes called "clickstream". This is the only information collected unless you voluntarily provide information to us.

We use clickstream information, which we may (subject to the relevant permissions) share with our affiliates, licensees, trusted vendors and companies who assist us in analyzing our site data and ways to improve user experience, only as anonymous aggregate data to determine the number of visitors to our website, to understand how visitors navigate our website, to determine common traffic patterns, including what site the visitor came from, to ensure that the website is working properly and to improve the design and content of our website. This aggregate information does not include individual names. For further information regarding cookies and how to disable them, refer to "Our Use of Cookies" below.

### Wireless Service:

When you use our wireless service, we automatically collect information about your use of the wireless service, including:

  * utilization data, e.g. # of users of service by store;
  * session data, e.g. date and time device entered store, length of session;
  * store data, e.g. address of store where device is used;
  * use of DXL services, e.g. mobile coupons redeemed; and
  * websites and pages visited, e.g. DestinationXL.com, google.com

Click here for our Wireless Terms of Use

### Information you give us:

Whenever you shop in our stores, use our wireless service, or shop online at DestinationXL.com, we will collect your IP Address and may ask you to provide voluntarily some personal information needed to better serve you and/or complete your transaction. This "Personal Information" may include: (i) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address and zip code); (ii) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number and billing address, if you use a credit or debit card or pay by check); and (iii) Demographic Data (such as your age, marital status and occupation).

  * If you search our website, make a purchase, communicate with any of our departments such as Customer Service, or choose to use or participate in one of our various services, promotions, programs, surveys or sweepstakes, we may collect additional information as mentioned above.
  * From your transactions and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning your personal preferences and the specific products or services you purchase or use.
  * We may also gather or receive information from other companies.

* * *

## SECURING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND FINANCIAL DATA

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to try to protect your Personal Information and financial data. An encryption methodology called TLS (Transport Layer Security) is used to help protect personal information that is transported via the Internet. For payment related data, DXL utilizes what we consider to be appropriate physical and technical access controls, and other information security methodologies and safeguards designed to improve data protection. For further information, click the "Back" button on your web browser and review our Security Statement.

While we strive to protect your Personal Information, no data transmission over the Internet, including e-mail and wireless service, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure against interception. Once we receive your transmission, we use our best effort to ensure its security on our systems, however, DXL cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our website, and therefore you use our website and wireless service at your own risk. If your proposed e-mail or wireless communication includes sensitive information such as your Social Security number or your account, credit or debit card number, we strongly encourage you not to send to it to us electronically, but to contact us by mail or telephone instead so that one of our customer service associates may gladly assist you.

* * *

## OUR USE OF COOKIES

DestinationXL.com uses cookies to collect website navigational information so that our Site, Blog, and Services can remember you and provide you with the information you're most likely to need. Site navigational information includes standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your IP address, and the actions you take on our Site (such as pages viewed and links clicked). Please note that some cookies last only for your current browser session, while others persist for longer periods of time. For instance, when you return to our Site, cookies identify you and prompt the site to provide your username (not your password), so you can sign in more quickly. We also use information gained through cookies to compile statistical information about use of our Site, such as the time users spend at the site and the pages they visit most often. Those statistics do not include Personal Information. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's "Help" menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Please note that if you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled which may make your site experience less efficient, and some of our Services and features may not function properly. To manage the use of targeting or advertising cookies on our Site or Blog, consult your individual browser settings for cookies. You can still shop and make purchases from DestinationXL.com even if you set your browser to reject cookies, however, we may not be able to provide you with as personalized a shopping experience.

* * *

## USING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use the information we collect for various purposes, including:

  * to complete your purchase transactions;
  * to provide the services you request, including to respond to your questions and requests for information;
  * to send you mail correspondence and other offerings;
  * to contact you about the status of your store, phone, or DestinationXL.com orders;
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you;
  * to provide information concerning products you have purchased;
  * to determine the effectiveness of our Internet presence and improve the functionality of our web site;
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience;
  * to enhance the effectiveness of our wireless service, analyzing how the wireless service is used and improving our stores and mobile experience;
  * banner ads and mobile coupons promoting our products and services and those of third parties;
  * for business analytics, reporting, governance and administrative purposes within our company;
  * to try to detect and prevent fraud and to try to protect the security of our systems and platforms; and
  * Legal compliance including: assist law enforcement and respond to legal/regulatory inquiries, enforce or ensure compliance with the DXL wireless terms of use, apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of DXL, our guests or others.

* * *

## INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH OTHERS

DXL shares the information we collect within DXL, which includes all DXL subsidiaries and trusted vendors and companies outside of DXL that we have authorized to send you promotional information about their products or services affiliated businesses so they can let you know about products or services we think might be of interest to you, and companies who assist us in analyzing our site data and ways to improve user experience; however, these parties do not have any independent right to share this information.

Further, we may employ other companies or individuals to provide some services to us such as IT and hosting services, analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, consulting, mobile support or other services. These third-parties will have access only to the information needed to perform their functions and cannot use that information for any other purpose. Also when you make a purchase via credit card, your information may be shared with payment card processors for the purpose of completing your transaction. We do not share your information in instances other than providing and completing services on your behalf. To ship and track your online purchases, we make your name and mailing address available to such companies as UPS, Federal Express and the U.S. Postal Service. DXL will NOT share your information with other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described elsewhere in this Privacy Statement or with your consent.

* * *

## LEGAL DISCLAIMER

Though DXL makes every effort to preserve the privacy of Personal Information, on rare occasions, we may disclose specific information with law enforcement or government officials upon request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

* * *

## CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Unless a parent or guardian consents in advance, DXL will not knowingly use information that a child provides to DXL for any direct marketing, advertising, selling or promotional purposes. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us at 855-ShopDXL (1-855-746-7395). Persons under the age of 17 should obtain their parents' permission prior to submitting any Personal Information to DXL or using our wireless service.

* * *

## YOUR CHOICES REGARDING THE TYPE OF INFORMATION YOU RECEIVE FROM DESTINATION XL

We offer choices regarding the type and occurrence of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive communications from DXL, or if you prefer to receive them less frequently, please:

  * Write to us at Destination XL, 555 Turnpike Street, Canton MA 02021; Attention: Customer Relations;
  * Call us toll-free at [1-855-ShopDXL(1-855-746-7395)](tel:1-855-746-7395);
  * Email us at [customerservice@DestinationXL.com](mailto:customerservice@DestinationXL.com).

You may also click the unsubscribe link on any e-mail communication you receive from us and follow the instructions on screen.

* * *

## YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you prefer that we NOT share your Personal Information with any of the trusted vendors and companies outside of DXL that we have authorized to send you promotional information about their products or services, you may "opt-out" by simply telling us when you give us your Personal Information, or please:

  * Write to us at Destination XL, 555 Turnpike Street, Canton MA 02021; Attention: Customer Relations;
  * Call us toll-free at [1-855-ShopDXL](tel:1-855-746-7395);
  * Email us at [customerservice@DestinationXL.com](mailto:customerservice@DestinationXL.com).

Please be sure to provide us with your exact name, mailing address and the nature of your request so that we can correctly identify you and properly fulfill your request. We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible.

You can still visit our website and choose not to provide us with Personal Information however, you would not be able to access and use those portions of the website that require your Personal Information, such as those necessary to make a purchase.

* * *

## YOUR ACCOUNT

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy and completeness of your Personal Information, as well as the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer and mobile device. You can edit your Personal Information at any time by using your DXL password to access your account.

* * *

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites that we think you will enjoy, but which are not under our control. Please take note that Destination XL is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such other websites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site they visit. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by DestinationXL.com.

* * *

## PRIVACY STATEMENT CHANGES

We may, from time to time, make changes to our Privacy Statement and post those changes here. We recommend that visitors of DestinationXL.com periodically visit this Privacy Statement to learn of new privacy practices or changes to our policy.

* * *

## FURTHER INFORMATION

If you would like further information, or have any questions about our Privacy Statement, please:

  * Write to us at Destination XL, 555 Turnpike Street, Canton MA 02021; Attention: Customer Relations;
  * Call us toll-free at [1-855-ShopDXL](tel:1-855-746-7395);
  * Email us at [customerservice@DestinationXL.com](mailto:customerservice@DestinationXL.com).

* * *

## NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS - Your California Privacy Rights

In addition to other rights described in this Privacy Statement, a California resident with whom DXL has an established business relationship and about whom DXL has disclosed such individual's Personal Information to third-parties for the third-parties' direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, shall have the right, subject to certain exceptions and our offering you the choice not to have your information shared as described above, to receive the following information within thirty (30) days of our receipt of the request:

  * The categories of Personal Information disclosed to such third-parties during the immediately preceding calendar year
  * The names and addresses of such third-parties with whom such Personal Information was shared during the preceding calendar year; and
  * If not apparent from the name, the nature of the business of such third-parties.

All requests for such information must be in writing and sent to:  
Destination XL, 555 Turnpike Street, Canton MA 02021; Attention: Customer Relations
